dreamhomeinthezone.com 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy | Jimmy John's Gourmet Sandwiches

This Policy was last updated on March 25, 2019.

### Overview

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to: the websites located at jimmyjohns.com, online.jimmyjohns.com, store.jimmyjohns.com, mercury-gift.com/JimmyJohns, Jimmy John's mobile applications, and any other websites or applications associated with the Jimmy John's brand or products that direct the viewer or user to this Policy (collectively, "Platforms"). In this Policy, the terms "we," "our," and "us" refers to Jimmy John's Franchisor SPV, LLC ("Jimmy John's"). Jimmy John's parent, subsidiary, and related companies are collectively referred to as affiliates ("Affiliates"). 

Jimmy John's is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information collected by or submitted to us through our Platforms. We believe it is important for you to know how we treat the information you share with us. This Policy will explain how your personal information will be treated as you use our Platforms and their features or place an order for products through our Platforms. Personal information includes any information you may provide to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail addresses or credit card information. This Policy is incorporated into, and part of, our [_Terms & Conditions _](https://www.jimmyjohns.com/terms-and-conditions/), which govern your use of our Platforms in general. 

Depending upon which of our services you are utilizing, the types of nonpublic personal information that we may collect include: (i) information we receive from you on applications, forms, and in other communications to us, whether in writing, in person, by telephone, or any other means; (ii) information about your transactions with us, our Affiliates, or others; and (iii) information we receive from a consumer reporting agency. 

This Policy does not govern the manner in which we may use information that we have obtained from any other source, such as information obtained from a public record or from another person or entity. 

By visiting our Platforms, you acknowledge and agree that you have read this Policy and agree to the collection, use, and other processing of your information in accordance with the practices described in this Policy. If you do not agree to all of the terms, conditions, and practices set forth herein, do not access our Platforms or any of their pages, do not place an order for products through our Platforms, or submit any personal or confidential information online. 

### How We Collect Your Information

Every time you visit us through one of our Platforms, our servers collect basic technical information. Generally, your e-mail address and all other personal information is collected only when you voluntarily provide that data while registering on our Platforms or for activities such as placing an online order, participating in surveys, or entering information on our Platforms. For example, we may collect your domain name, the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to Jimmy John's and your browser and operating system. We do this using cookies, pixels, web beacons, and/or GIF files. "Cookies" are small text files that identify an individual computer's browser entering a website or other information about a website user, and are stored on a user's hard drive. They allow the site to track that browser's movement through the site over several sessions. 

If you do not want a cookie placed on your computer as a result of using our Platforms, you may disable cookies altogether by modifying the Preferences section of your Internet browser. If you reject the cookie, you may be unable to use portions of our Platforms that require registration, some pages on our Platforms might not function properly, and the Platform experience will not be capable of being tailored to you from visit to visit. If you have no problem accepting cookies, but wish to be informed of their use, you may turn on a warning prompt by modifying the cookie warning section also located in the Preferences section of your Internet browser. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information about how to turn cookies on and off for your browser. Cookies are placed on your computer, and, accordingly, we do not store cookies on our computers, but may forward them to external parties. 

In addition, our Platforms use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help our Platforms analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of our Platforms (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our Platforms, compiling reports on website activity for website operators, and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, or by enabling the Do Not Track settings in your browser, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our Platforms. By using our Platforms, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

### How We Use Your Information

The information you provide helps Jimmy John's understand how you use our Platforms and our products and services. This allows us to recognize your needs and continue to make the improvements that are important to you and our customers. 

Jimmy John's and its Affiliates may use your information to: respond to specific inquiries or requests; fulfill your orders and to process your transactions; send notices, offers, and solicitations that may take the form of U.S. mail, telephone calls, e-mail, social media, and other methods of contact; and for internal analysis in order to improve our products and services. We may share your e-mail address or mailing address with our Affiliates and service providers for these purposes (for more information please see the section entitled **Sharing Information** below). If you do not want us to send you mail or e-mail, or to call you to provide you with such promotional information, please see the section entitled **Your Information and Opting-Out below**. 

From time to time, we may offer promotions or special opportunities on our Platforms. When you enter a promotion, or respond to such opportunity, we will require the submission of your name, e-mail address, and postal address. We will use this personally identifiable information for purposes of managing the promotion or opportunity in accordance with its rules, and may share this information with our Affiliates and service providers (for more information please see the section entitled **Sharing Information** below). 

### Survey

Jimmy John's often conducts online surveys of visitors. Your participation in a survey is voluntary and the information you provide will not be shared with third parties (other than our Affiliates) unless you have received prior notification upon the collection of your feedback. 

### Children's Policy

Jimmy John's is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors under the age of 18. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a minor, we may use your personal information to obtain parental consent for the minor's use of our Platforms. Parents should supervise the online activities of their children, and consider the use of tools available from online services and software providers that help provide kid-friendly Internet environments. 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, and we do not specifically market to, children under the age of 13 years old. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use our Platforms. 

### Sharing Information

In the course of carrying out our operations and seeking to improve the content on our Platforms, we may transfer your personally identifiable information and other information that you submit through our Platforms to our offices, Affiliates, and service providers in the United States. We will not sell, exchange, or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to the extent required by law, in accordance with your instructions, or as set out below: 

  * **Transaction Requirements:** We sometimes retain the services of third parties to perform functions or services on our behalf. We will require that these companies not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. However, we do not undertake to confirm, investigate, or police their practices. 
  * **Affiliated Companies:** We may also provide all of the types of nonpublic personal information listed above to one or more of our Affiliates and service providers. Such service providers include, without limitation, financial entities, insurers, vendors, and/or companies involved in the food services business. Furthermore, we may also provide all the information that we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, on behalf of our Affiliates, or to other institutions with whom we or our Affiliates have joint marketing agreements. 
  * **Joint Promotions:** From time to time, we may join with third parties to provide specific services or products. When users sign up for these services or order these products, we will share only the names and other information that is necessary for the third parties to provide these services or products. These third parties are not permitted to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services or products. However, we do not undertake to confirm, investigate, or police their practices. 
  * **Protection of Site and Others:** We may preserve, and have the right to disclose, any information about you or your use of our Platforms without your prior permission if we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of us, our Affiliates, other users of our Platforms, or the public; and/or (ii) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third-parties. We also may disclose information as we deem necessary to: (1) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (2) pursue available remedies or limit damages we may sustain; and (3) enforce our [_Terms & Conditions_](https://www.jimmyjohns.com/terms-and-conditions/). 

We will share aggregated demographic information with our Affiliates and other third parties. This type of information is not linked to any personally identifiable information that can identify any individual person. 

### Other Disclosure of Personal Information

Jimmy John's will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this Policy, or (ii) as required by law. In the event that Jimmy John's goes through a business transition, such as a merger, another company acquires Jimmy John's or its Affiliates, or Jimmy John's sells a portion of its assets, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be given the choice to opt out. 

### Other Sites

Our Platforms may contain links to other sites on the Web. Unless otherwise expressly stated in the terms and conditions of use for such websites, all such websites are not owned, operated, or controlled by Jimmy John's and shall be governed by their own terms and conditions and privacy policy and not this Policy. We cannot control, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices or content of such other websites. Jimmy John's encourages you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Policy is made a part of our [_Website Terms & Conditions_](https://www.jimmyjohns.com/terms-and-conditions/). 

Jimmy John's iOS App uses the Google Places API for iOS which incorporates Google's Privacy Policy found at the following link [_http://www.google.com/privacy.html_](https://www.google.com/privacy.html). 

### Your Information and Opting-Out

If you do not wish to receive periodic mailings or e-mails, or telephone contact concerning our Platforms or our products or services, you may opt-out of receiving such marketing or promotional communications by sending us a written request to the address listed below, or by following the opt-out instructions in the e-mail you receive from us. However, if you choose to opt-out of marketing or promotional communications, we reserve the right to contact you regarding technical support and any other matter that might affect our service to you, and/or your use of our Platforms, as applicable. For information about the Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out programs, please visit: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>. 

### Unsubscribe and Data Remove Policies

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, e-mail, or postal address), or if you no longer desire our services, feel free to correct, update, or delete/deactivate your personally identifiable information. This can be done by e-mailing our Customer Support at [_[email  protected]_](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#84e2e1e1e0e6e5e7efc4eeede9e9fdeeebeceaf7aae7ebe9). 

### E-Mail and Contact Forms

Please be aware that when you receive a receipt acknowledging your email or use of our customer service or application web forms, it means that the message has been routed into the Internet, and not that the message has been received by us. Jimmy John's may retain the content of any customer inquiry or e-mail, or employment service or application web form or email that Jimmy John's receives, the email address from which it is sent, and our response. Content and other information related to e-mails sent by users to Jimmy John's may be used as testimonials or for other marketing purposes in accordance with the [_Terms & Conditions_](https://www.jimmyjohns.com/terms-and-conditions/). 

### Site Security

We have reasonable and appropriate security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuses, and alteration of your personally identifiable information under our control. In all cases, we have taken reasonable steps to confirm that the information is retained in secured facilities and that reasonable measures have been implemented for protection from unauthorized access. All personal information accepted on our Platforms is encrypted and secured through the use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our Platforms or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We ask that you do your part by maintaining the strict confidentiality of any computer passwords you use to access the Internet or our Platforms. 

If you believe that you have discovered a security issue or vulnerability on any of our Platforms, please contact us at [_[email  protected]_](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ed84838b829e888ead8784808094878285839ec38e8280). 

### Who Do I Ask If I Have Any Additional Questions?

If you have any further questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy and our use of personal information, please send them to [_[email  protected]_](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a7c1c2c2c3c5c6c4cce7cdcecacadecdc8cfc9d489c4c8ca). 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. Changes to this Policy will be effective when posted. In case of a material change to the Policy, we will provide notice on our Platforms of any update to the Policy and post the updated Policy. You are responsible for reviewing the current policy when you visit our site. Your continued use of our Platforms is an acknowledgment and consent to any terms contained in this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. Even if you are no longer a customer, our Policy will continue to apply to the information you provided to us. If, however, we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. By using our Platforms, you acknowledge and agree that you have read this Policy and agree to the collection, use, and other processing of your information in accordance with the practices described in this Policy. If you do not agree to all of the terms, conditions, and practices set forth herein, you should cease use of the site immediately.
